Bras are bras.
As much as you might want to have some innovative design it is ultimately a bra.
And not that I'm trying to make you not want to be creative with it but what I think of is bathing suit types.
If it's going to be a bathing suit, if it's going to be a bra I want it along the same sort of lines.
I want my underwear that I design to be able to be worn Madonna style, outside of the clothes and look good.
I don't want it to be just regular so I always include some sort of design variation.
Such as the diagonals on this bra which makes it look kind of more swimsuit inspired.
And with this bra I decided not to do any under wire shaping.
It's going to be all one piece.
There's no mid section.
It's a sports bra with a dip.
A cross between a sports bra and then a regular bra bra.
But it's all one piece.
So you start out with your shoulder straps.
Figure out what width you want them and where you want them.
And since it's all one piece you have and actual neckline.
The chest part dips.
Figure out where you want it to dip.
Obviously in the middle of the chest.
Make sure it falls in the middle of the chest.
And then create your cups.
And then do your design variations.
And there you go.